<div xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://hl7.org/fhir ../../src-generated/schemas/fhir-single.xsd" lang="en">
  <a name="scope">  </a>
	<p>
    This ImplementationGuide captures our Way of Working: the techniques, constraints and pratices that we use when making FHIR-based specifications for use in Belgium. 
   </p>
	<blockquote class="stu-note">
	<strong>This documentation is always being developed. Do not expect it to be 'stable' - rather, please provide feedback to enhance it.</strong>
	</blockquote>
	<p> </p>
  <h3>Content</h3> <a name="content"> </a>
	<p/>

<p>This specification contains the Way of Working for making ImplementationGuides.</p>
<p></p>
<p></p>

<a name="navigation"> </a>
<p>The top menu allows quick navigation to the different sections, and a <a href="toc.html">Table of Contents</a> is provided with the entire content of this Implementation Guide. (Be aware that some pages have multiple tabs).</p>
<p></p>
	<a name="ip"> </a>
	<h3>Intellectual Property Considerations</h3>
	<p>
    While this implementation guide and the underlying FHIR are licensed as public domain, this guide includes examples making use of terminologies such 
    as LOINC, SNOMED CT and others which have more restrictive licensing requirements. Implementers should make themselves familiar with licensing and 
    any other constraints of terminologies, questionnaires, and other components used as part of their implementation process. In some cases, 
    licensing requirements may limit the systems that data captured using certain questionnaires may be shared with.
  </p>
	<p>
    Similarly to the HL7 FHIR community, the HL7 Community prefers the use of open source with commercial-friendly licenses. This specific implementation Guide is under a Attribute CC By license, which allows others to distribute, remix, tweak, and build upon this work, even commercially, as long as they credit the source for the original creation.
  </p>

	<a name="disclaimer"> </a>
	<h3>Disclaimer</h3>
	<p>
    This documentation is provided without warranty of completeness or consistency.
    No liability can be inferred from the use or misuse of this documentation, or its consequences.
  </p>
</div>